mercedesamgf1.com 2017-01-27

# MERCEDES AMG PETRONAS - Contact

### Contact

### Website Terms and Conditions

[www.mercedesamgf1.com](https://www.mercedesamgf1.com/) is the official website of Mercedes-Benz Grand Prix Ltd

The use of this Website is subject to the following terms and conditions. By using this Website you accept the following terms and conditions.

**Legal notice**

Copyright Mercedes-Benz Grand Prix Limited or Mercedes AMG PETRONAS Formula One Team. '). All rights reserved. The text, images, logos, trademarks, graphics, sound files, animation files, video files and their arrangements are subject to copyrights and other intellectual property protection. The MGP Marks may not be used without our prior written permission.

MGP Marks may only be used for personal use and may not be used or distributed in any way for commercial use. MGP Marks may not be re posted on other internet websites.

This Website may contain images, text, logos, trademarks, graphics, sound files, animation files, video files and video arrangements belonging to our partners and/or sponsors. Any Sponsor's and Partner's Marks used on this site are used with their permission. They may not be used or copied for any commercial purposes.

**Trademarks**

All trademarks referred to on this website are owned and controlled by MGP, its affiliates and/or sponsors/partners (known collectively as 'Companies'.

**No licences**

We hope that you enjoy the Website as much as we do. However, the Companies must take appropriate steps to protect their intellectual property. Please note that, this Website, and/or any material contained within this Website, does not and shall not, in any way, grant to any person a licence to the Companies' intellectual property or any part of it.

**No warranties or representations**

This Website is presented to you “AS IS,” without any representation or warranty of any kind including implied or express warranties regarding the quality of the Website and/or its fitness for any particular purpose. We aim to provide an excellent service free from any errors but we cannot guarantee that the Website will always be available and/or free from errors. To the extent permitted by law, neither the Companies nor any of them accept any liability arising from any errors and/or unavailability from our Website.

We aim to publish accurate information at all times and will update information on a regular basis. If you become aware of any inaccuracies on our Website, please contact us on the details below.

We use security measures to protect the contents of the Website from viruses. However, we cannot guarantee that material and downloads from our Website are free from viruses or malicious codes. It is your responsibility to ensure that you have taken precautions to protect your own computer system from virus infections.

Please be aware that this Website contains video messages, reports, audio files, and forward-looking statements that may reflect management's current views and views in relation to future events. These projects and views are only statements and opinions of that person and are subject to risks and uncertainties. We do not intend to update any forward-looking statements and they are made at the date on which they are made. No reliability must be placed on these statements, they are not factual and merely opinions.

**Links to external sites**

This Website contains linked to external sites which may not be under the control of the Companies. Therefore we do not accept any responsibility for the contents of any linked site. The Website only provides you with these links solely as convenience to you.

**Liability**

Nothing in these terms of use excludes liability for death, personal injury arising from our negligence or fraudulent misrepresentation or any other liability that cannot be excluded or limited by English Law. We do not accept liability for direct or indirect losses arising from your use of his Website.

**Cookies**

The Website uses cookies to allow MGP to gather information about how we can improve the Website. More information on how we use these cookies can be found in our Cookies Policy here.

If you require further information please write to:

**Mercedes-Benz Grand Prix Ltd, Operations Centre, Brackley, Northants, NN13 7BD, England or enquries@mercedesamgf1.com**

Mercedes-Benz Grand Prix Limited is registered in England, registration number 787446. Last updated on 13 August 2014.

©2015 Mercedes-Benz Grand Prix Limited. All rights reserved.

### Cookie Policy

### Mercedes-Benz Grand Prix Limited T/A Mercedes AMG PETRONAS Formula One Team ('MGP') - Cookies Policy ('Policy')

**(1) What are Cookies?**

MGP uses cookies to record preferences of visitors. This enables MGP to optimise the design of its website. A cookie is a small file, typically of letters and numbers, downloaded on to a device when the user accesses our website. A cookie is stored on your hard drive.

Cookies are useful, they ease navigation, and allow us to recognise your device. Cookies enable us to identify the most common and popular sections of our website and so enable us to provide information to you that is appropriate, whilst also allowing us to improve the service that we provide to you. MGP is constantly seeking to provide you with a better service and therefore we use cookies.

**By continuing on to this website, you automatically consent to the use of cookies in accordance with this Policy.**

**(2) Personal details**

Cookies may store personal data such as email addresses and passwords. This will allow the site to ensure that you don’t have to re-enter log in details and passwords on numerous occasions.

**(3) Non-acceptance of Cookies**

You do not have to consent to cookies when you are prompted. You are able to remove cookies, a step by step guide to removal of cookies can be found on http://www.aboutcookies.org. This site can also provide further information on cookies.

Please note, by not accepting cookies, there may be reduced availability of services on this website.

MGP is committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent any unauthorised disclosure, we collect the above information and store it in a secure database.

**(4) Cookies that MGP use fall into the following categories**

**Session Cookies** \- these allow websites to link the actions of a user during a browsing session. These cookies are essential to enable the user to use the features of a website and allow the access of secure areas of the website. Services cannot be provided without the acceptance of these particular types of cookies. These cookies expire after the browsing session and do not need to be stored long term.

**Persistent Cookies** \- these allow preferences across our website or other websites to be stored and remembered. This will allow advertising to be targeted from information that has been collected. It also allows our website to information such as language preference. These cookies will remain on your device until they are deleted.

**Third Party Cookies** \- these cookies are placed by organisations other than MGP. This may be because there are pages on our site embedded from third party websites. If these pages are from another website we can unfortunately not control these third party cookies. If you would like to change these third party cookies, you should visit their website and check their information on how to manage their cookies.

**Please note that MGP uses all three types of cookies. Use of the website indicates your acceptance to this Policy.**

If you require further information please write to:

**Mercedes-Benz Grand Prix Ltd, Operations Centre, Brackley, Northants, NN13 7BD, England or enquries@mercedesamgf1.com**

Mercedes-Benz Grand Prix Limited is registered in England, registration number 787446. Last updated on 13 August 2014.

©2015 Mercedes-Benz Grand Prix Limited. All rights reserved.

### Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy ('Policy') – Mercedes-Benz Grand Prix Limited, trading as Mercedes AMG PETRONAS Formula One Team ('MGP')

**Your Privacy**

MGP is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. If it is necessary for you to provide personal information, you can be assured that that information will only be used in accordance with this Policy. To ensure that you understand how your information will be used please read this Policy in full.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the “Act”), the data controller is MGP of Operations Centre, Brackley, Northamptonshire, NN13 7BD.

Please note, we reserve the right to amend this Policy at any time, normally by posting an updated Policy on this page and, where appropriate, notifying to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to this Policy.

**Why we collect personal information**

MGP collects and uses your personal information as set out in this Policy including to give you superior fan experience and to provide you with convenient access to our products and services. MGP also uses your personal information to keep you up-to-date on the latest product announcements, general updates, special offers and other exciting information that we think you might like to hear about. MGP also uses your personal information to deliver offers and communications tailored to you as an individual and to provide a personalised fan experience.

**How we collect your personal information**

Information you give us: We may collect your personal information including in the following circumstances:

  * when you correspond with us;
  * when you participate in a promotion or survey;
  * when you sign up to a mailing list;
  * when you sign up or subscribe for any MGP service (including, without limitation, when you register on the MGP website (“Website”) and/or download MGP’s mobile smart phone application (“Mobile Application”));
  * when you participate in any prize draws or competitions;
  * when you participate in discussion boards or other social media functions operated by us or on our behalf;  
when you search for a product or place an order with us including on the Website and other sites we control; and
  * when you report a problem with our Website or other sites we control.

The information you give us may include, without limitation, your first name, surname, address, e-mail address, location, source, phone number, birthday, financial and credit card information, personal description and photograph.

**Information we collect about you:** With regard to each of your visits to our Website, or other sites we control, we may automatically collect the following information:

  * technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform; and
  * information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our Website, and other sites we control, (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to call our customer service number.

Please note that the above types of information are intended only to be illustrative and do not comprise an exhaustive list.

**Information we receive from other sources:** We may receive information about you if you use any of the other websites we operate or the other services we provide. We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, marketing agents, sub-contractors in technical, payment, order fulfilment, and delivery services, advertising and marketing networks, analytics, database and applications providers and search information providers) and may receive information about you from them. 

**How we use your personal information**

**Information you give us:** We will use this information:

  * to present our Website, Mobile Application and other MGP digital platforms, to you;
  * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with information, products or services that you request;
  * to provide you with information about other goods and services and events we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about;
  * to provide you with information about goods and/or services we feel may interest you. If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale or negotiations of a sale to you, or where you have otherwise provided your consent. If you do not want us to use your data in this way, please contact us at the address provided at the bottom of this Policy;
  * to operate and maintain an internal database of our fans, and to gather a profile on our fans, so we might better understand what interests you, and how we can better tailor our updates, goods, services and opportunities for you, including for the purposes set out in this privacy policy;
  * to notify you about changes to our Website, Mobile Application and/or other sites or any products or services that we offer or provide through it (including, without limitation, when you register for our Website, Mobile Application and/or other sites);
  * to ensure that content from our Website, Mobile Application and/or other sites, is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer or device; and
  * for any other purpose with your consent.

**Information we collect about you:** We will use this information:

  * to administer our Website, Mobile Application and other sites, and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
  * to improve our Website, Mobile Application and other sites, to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer or device; 
  * to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;
  * as part of our efforts to keep our Website, Mobile Application and other sites, safe and secure;
  * to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you; and
  * to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our Website, Mobile Application and other sites, about goods or services that may interest you or them.

**Information we receive from other sources:** We may combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We may use this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).

Please note that the above comprises a non-exhaustive list of circumstances where MGP may collect and/or use your personal information. There may be other circumstances where MGP collects your personal information but you will be made aware of such collection at the time.

MGP is committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent any unauthorised disclosure, we collect the above information and store it in a secure database.

**When we disclose your personal information**

We may share your personal information with any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the English Companies Act 2006.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;
  * if MGP or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it will be one of the transferred assets;
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use or terms and conditions of supply and other agreements from time to time; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of MGP, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction; and/or
  * where we use analytics database and applications providers and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our Website, Mobile Application and other sites.

Unless you have provided your consent, we will not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our team partners, team suppliers and/or other advertisers or sponsors, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 200 men aged under 25 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women located in a particular part of the country). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' or sponsors’ wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.

Other examples of instances where MGP may wish to share your information may include (without limitation):

  * information provided to shipping companies so that they can deliver products;
  * information provided to third party companies who may execute competitions or prize draws or marketing or social media campaigns on our behalf, and/or who may administer our fan databases;
  * information provided to third party companies who may collate results from surveys on our behalf; and/or
  * information to third party companies who may execute other services on our behalf from time to time.

All of our employees, agencies, partners and suppliers are obliged by us to respect confidentiality.

We may disclose personal information to other parties not listed above if we are required by law to do so.

**How we protect and store your personal information**

MGP safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic and managerial procedures. MGP requests that you take reasonable steps to safeguard and protect your own personal data when you are on the internet. Change passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers and make sure that you use a secure browser.

The web server may automatically record your IP address and the date and length of time you spent on our Website, and other sites, including as detailed in the “Information we collect about you” sections above.

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ('EEA'). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers or partners. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, management of our fan database, the fulfilment of any order made by you, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Website, and other sites; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

**Links to other sites**

MGP will endeavour to only provide links to other sites that are from a trustworthy source. However, once you leave the Website or other sites we control, you should be aware and take note that we have no control over any other website. We cannot, therefore, be responsible for the protection of privacy of any information, that you provide on any other website. Those websites, including, without limitation, those of MGP’s webstore operator, will not be governed by this Policy. If you use any of the links provided to you from our site, you should read their applicable privacy statement before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**Social Plugins**

MGP uses social plugins of social networks such as: Facebook, Google+, Twitter and Instagram ('Buttons').

When you visit the Website, these Buttons will be deactivated by default. To activate these Buttons you must click on them. Once they have been clicked they will remain active until they are deactivated by you or you delete your cookies.

When the Button is activated, the social network can extract data independently, whether you interact with the Button or not. If you are logged on to a social network, the network can assign your visit to the Website, or our other sites, to your user social network account. 

MGP has no control on the data retrieved by social networking websites and you must consult their relevant social network privacy policy, or data protection policy, to find out how they use your data. For the avoidance of doubt this Policy only relates to the Website and other channels, networks, mobile applications, platforms and/or social media accounts operated by MGP or on MGP’s behalf.

If you do not want to combine data extracted from your own personal networking site, and our Website or other sites, please ensure that you log out of any social network sites before activating the Buttons.

**Cookies**

The Website uses cookies to allow MGP to gather information about how we can improve the Website. More information on how we use these cookies can be found in our Cookies Policy [here](https://www.mercedesamgf1.com/en/mercedes-amg-f1/imprint/#cookie-policy).

**Your Rights**

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will inform you if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by contacting us at address below.

**Access to information**

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. Any request should be made in writing and the best way for you to do so is to contact us at the address stated below. As MGP must be able to identify the person making the request, and because a fee may be due, MGP requests that you confirm any request made by you via different means by contacting us at the address stated below. Due to technological constraints and/or information security considerations, it may be inappropriate to use social media to supply information in response to any request by you for access to information, and so please provide an alternative delivery address for our response.

**Contact**

All comments, queries and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcome. Please direct them to:

MERCEDES AMG PETRONAS Formula OneTM Team, Operations Centre, Brackley, Northamptonshire NN13 7BD marked for the attention of the Legal Department

Or [legal@mercedesamgf1.com](mailto:legal@mercedesamgf1.com).

Mercedes-Benz Grand Prix Ltd. is registered in England, registration number 787446

©2016 Mercedes-Benz Grand Prix Ltd. All rights reserved.

This privacy policy was last updated on 1 November 2016
